I'm in Visual Studio Code and I would like to apply clang-format to my hello.cpp file.
我在 Visual Studio 代码中 我希望将 cloang格式应用于 hello.cpp 文件
So I'm going to go to the extensions and I'm going to search for clang-format,
所以我要去扩建我要去寻找克隆格式
and I'm going to install it.
我要去安装它
Now, it's installed and it says,
现在它已经安装好了
"Files can be formatted on-demand by right-clicking in
"可以通过右键单击文件来格式化文件
the document and selecting format document,
文档和选择格式文档
or by using the associated keyboard shortcut usually Ctrl Shift F on Windows,
或在 Windows上使用关联的键盘快捷键 ( 通常是 Ctrl Shift F )
Ctrl Shift I on Linux,
Linux 上的 Ctrl Shift I
and Shift Command F on Mac OS.
以及在 Mac OS上的 Shift Command F
So I'm on Linux, so I want Ctrl Shift I.
所以我在 Linux 上 所以我想要 Ctrl Shift I
Now, if I come here to hello.cpp and I hit Ctrl Shift I,
现在 如果我来到 hello.cpp 并点击 Ctrl Shift I
clang-format actually puts my one line, "Hello World!"
clang-format 实际放置我的一行 "Hello World!"
implementation on the same line as my function signature.
与我的函数特征符在同一行上的实现
If I save this and I compile it and run it,
如果我保存了这个我编译它然后运行它
everything should still work but I have clang-format's default formatting style.
一切都应该起作用 但我有克隆格式的默认格式化样式